Digital Collections and Archives Records UA069
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Publications, 2001 -- 2010; UA069.003; 0.2 Linear Feet
  - Tufts regional Fedora conference folder, 2010 July 20; UA069.003.010.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Tufts regional Fedora conference materials, 2010 July 20; UA069.003.010.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Tufts University by Anne Sauer, 2001; UA069.003.010.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Grants and projects records, 2002 -- 2012; UA069.004; 0.6 Linear Feet; 18 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains files relating to grants and other Digital Collections and Archives projects, including the "Fedora and the Preservation of University Records" project and the Tufts Accessioning Program for Electronic Records (TAPER). Material dates from 2002-2012.
  This series is organized into two subseries: Fedora and the Preservation of University Records (NHPRC): Final Reports; and TAPER.
  - Fedora and the Preservation of University Records (NHPRC): Final Reports, 2002 -- 2012; UA069.004.001; 0.47 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
    This series contains material relating to "Fedora and the Preservation of University Records," a project funded by a National Historical Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC) grant and conducted jointly with Yale University to investigate the preservation of electronic records. This series includes application paperwork, drafts of the grant, notes, and meeting materials. Dates for the items in this series range from 2002-2007.
    - 1.1 Project Overview, Version 1.0, 2006; UA069.004.001.00001; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
      An introduction to the project and outline of reports. National Historical Publications and Records Commission
      Electronic records; Digital preservation
    - 1.2 System Model, Version 1.0, 2006; UA069.004.001.00002; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
      A description of the components that comprise a recordkeeping system, preservation activities, and the relationship between recordkeeping systems and preservation activities. National Historical Publications and Records Commission
    - 1.3 Concerns, Version 1.0, 2006; UA069.004.001.00003; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
      Six attributes implicit in all requirements of the Requirements for Trustworthy Recordkeeping Systems and the Preservation of Electronic Records in a University Setting, and all the steps in the Ingest Guide and the Maintain Guide.National Historical Publications and Records Commission
    - 1.4 Glossary, Version 1.0, 2006; UA069.004.001.00004; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
      Definition of terms used throughout all project reports. Most capitalized words in the project reports are terms defined in the Glossary.
    - 1.5 Requirements for Trustworthy Recordkeeping Systems and the Preservation of Electronic Records in a University Setting, Version 1.0, 2006; UA069.004.001.00005; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
      Requirements for trustworthy recordkeeping systems and requirements for preservation activities.
    - 2.1 Ingest Guide, Version 1.0, 2006; UA069.004.001.00006; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
      A guide defining the necessary steps for a trustworthy Ingest process and a description of the resources needed to operate this process in a semi-automated manner.
    - 2.2 Ingest Projects, Version 1.0, 2006; UA069.004.001.00007; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
      An examination of three ingest projects undertaken according to the Ingest Guide.
    - 2.3 Ingest Tools, Version 1.0, 2006; UA069.004.001.00008; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
      A description of the Ingest tools examined and developed by project staff, including the Tufts Ingest Prototype System (TIPS).
    - 3.1 Maintain Guide, Version 1.0, 2006; UA069.004.001.00009; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
      A guide defining the necessary steps for a trustworthy maintain process.
    - 3.2 Checklist of Fedora's Ability to Support Maintain Activities, Version 1.0, 2006; UA069.004.001.00010; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
      A description of abstract services needed to support steps described in the Maintain Guide and an analysis of Fedora's ability to support these services.
    - 4.1 Analysis of Fedora's Ability to Support Preservation Activities, Version 1.0, 2006; UA069.004.001.00011; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
      An overview of Fedora's ability to support services needed for preservation activities and Fedora's current and potential role in records preservation.
    - 4.2 Conclusions and Future Directions, Version 1.0, 2006; UA069.004.001.00012; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
      A general discussion of project findings and opportunities for building on the work of this project.
    - Project Narrative, 2004 -- 2005; UA069.004.001.00013; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
      This project was completed in 2006.
    - Revised Plan of Work, 2003 -- 2009; UA069.004.001.00014; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
    - Interim Narrative Report, 2001 -- 2005; UA069.004.001.00015; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
    - Interim Narrative Report, 2005 -- 2008; UA069.004.001.00016; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
    - Interim Narrative Report, 2002 -- 2006; UA069.004.001.00017; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
    - Final Narrative Report, 2006 -- 2012; UA069.004.001.00018; Fedora and the Preservation of University Records Project (Box 1)
    - Grant close-out materials, 2006 -- 2007; UA069.004.001.009.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 85)
      75 years from date of creation.
    - NHPRC grant paperwork, 2005 -- 2006; UA069.004.001.009.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - NHPRC financial subcontract, 2005 July 15; UA069.004.001.009.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Final NHPRC narrative report, 2006 January 24; UA069.004.001.009.00081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - Yale visit agendas, circa 2005 -- 2006; UA069.004.001.009.00082; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - NHPRC notes and drafts, 2002 -- 2003; UA069.004.001.009.00083; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - No-cost extension materials, 2005 October - December; UA069.004.001.009.00084; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - NHPRC performance objectives correspondence, 2006 September 29; UA069.004.001.009.00085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - NHPRC grant planning materials, circa 2003; UA069.004.001.009.00086; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - NHPRC final application, circa 2003; UA069.004.001.009.00087; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Tufts-Yale general materials, 2004 -- 2005; UA069.004.001.009.00088; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Tufts-Yale meeting materials, 2004 August 30; UA069.004.001.009.00089; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Thorney meeting materials, 2005 September 14 -- 15; UA069.004.001.009.00090; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - NHPRC meeting materials, 2005 July 25; UA069.004.001.009.00091; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Nancy McGovern comments, 2006 February - March; UA069.004.001.009.00092; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - NHPRC grant administration materials, 2003 -- 2005; UA069.004.001.009.00093; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - NHPRC notification records, 2003 -- 2004; UA069.004.001.009.00094; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - NHPRC response materials, circa 2003; UA069.004.001.009.00095; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - NHPRC final copy, circa 2003; UA069.004.001.009.00096; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - TAPER, 2007 -- 2011; UA069.004.002; 0.13 Linear Feet
    This series contains material relating to the Tufts Accessioning Program for Electronic Records (TAPER), a three-year project funded by the National Historical Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC). During the project, DCA designed, developed, and implemented machine-readable submission agreements and records context records. This includes correspondence, budget materials, and proposals for the Program Expansion Project grant (called ProExpansion). Appleseed Software was the developer for this project and their role is reflected in the documentation. Material in this series ranges from 2007 -2011.
    - TAPER budget materials, 2010 -- 2011; UA069.004.002.009.00097; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - TAPER correspondence and data map, 2011 March 16; UA069.004.002.009.00098; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - TAPER XML consultant materials, 2008 -- 2009; UA069.004.002.009.00099; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Appleseed Software Consulting draft contract, 2008 October 22; UA069.004.002.009.00100; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - TAPER materials, 2007 -- 2008; UA069.004.002.009.00101; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - TAPER Appleseed materials, 2007 -- 2008; UA069.004.002.009.00102; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - TAPER XML consultant bids materials, 2008 September; UA069.004.002.009.00103; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - ProExpansion proposal materials, circa 2007; UA069.004.002.009.00104; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - ProExpansion proposal reviews, circa 2007; UA069.004.002.009.00105; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 112)
- Digital objects, 1662 -- 2015; 2000 -- 2004; UA069.005; 542 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains digital objects created by Digital Collections and Archives staff derived from collection material that transcend the original material significantly, or that are born-digital objects.
  This series is arranged chronologically, in order of creation
  - Concise Encyclopedia of Tufts History, 2000 -- 2004; UA069.005.DO.00001
    The encyclopedia seeks to capture more than 150 years of Tufts' achievements, societal contributions and outstanding alumni and faculty in concise entries. As a source of accurate factual information, the Encyclopedia can be used by anyone interested in the history of Tufts and of the people who have made it the unique institution it is.
    Tufts University -- History
  - The Boston directory. Embracing the city record, a general directory of the citizens, and a special directory of trades, professions, etc., with an almanac ..., 1855; UA069.005.DO.00002; Adams, George
    This version contains a full text transcription of the A-Z personal directory and images of advertisements, business directories, and additional content included in the original printed edition.
    Boston(Mass.)-Directories
  - Light on the hill: A history of Tufts College, 1852-1952, 1986; UA069.005.DO.00003; Miller, Russell
    Light on the Hill, the history of Tufts College, was published to coincide with the centennial of the institution in 1952. A second volume was published in 1986. This edition was created from the 1966 edition of Light on the Hill, Volume I.
  - Atlas of the county of Suffolk, Massachusetts. Volume 1. Boston proper, 1874; UA069.005.DO.00004; Hopkins, G. M. (Griffith Morgan)
    Boston (Mass.) - Maps.; Suffolk County (Mass.) -Maps.; Real property - Massachusetts - Suffolk County - Maps.; Landowners - Massachusetts - Suffolk County - Maps.
  - The Boston Directory for the year commencing July 1, 1925. Embracing the city record, a general directory of the citizens, and a special directory of trades, professions, with an almanac...", UA069.005.DO.00005; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    This version contains a full text transcription of the A-Z personal directory and images of advertisements included in the original printed edition.
  - Die Winterreise lyrics in German and French, 1827, UA069.005.DO.00006; Schubert, Franz; Youens, Susan
    Side-by-side display of the lyrics to the songs in Die Winterriese cycle in German and French.
    Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 1, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00001; Schubert, Franz
    Page image of lyrics from Die Winterreise in German and French.
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 2, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00002; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 3, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00003; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 4, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00004; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 5, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00005; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 6, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00006; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 7, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00007; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 8, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00008; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 9, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00009; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 10, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00010; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 11, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00011; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 12, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00012; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 13, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00013; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 14, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00014; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 15, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00015; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 16, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00016; Schubert, Franz
  - Die Winterreise lyrics, page 17, 2004; UA069.005.DO.00006.00017; Schubert, Franz
  - The production, promulgation, and politics of opera in France during the Enlightenment, 1662 -- 1774; UA069.005.DO.00007; Brown, Bruce Alan
    Delivered as part of the Ritter Colloquium Series sponsored by the Department of Music at Tufts University, October 17, 2003.
    - Frederic Louis Ritter, UA069.005.DO.00007.00001; Unknown
      Illustration for Bruce Brown's paper, The production, promulgation, and politics of opera in France during the Enlightenment.
      People; Ritter, Frederick Louis
    - Portrait of Louis XIV, 1662; UA069.005.DO.00007.00002; Mignard, P.
      People; Louis XIV
    - Portrait of Lully, UA069.005.DO.00007.00003; Mignard, P.
      People
    - Charles-Simon Favart, UA069.005.DO.00007.00004
      People; Favart, Charles-Simon
    - Favart, Thesee, cast & beginning, 1745; UA069.005.DO.00007.00005
      Music; Favart, Charles-Simon
    - Favart, Thesee, parodie, page 10-11, 1745; UA069.005.DO.00007.00006
    - Cythè assiégée, UA069.005.DO.00007.00007
      Music; Theater
    - Rameau - portrait by Aved, UA069.005.DO.00007.00008
    - Monsigny, Le Roi et le fermier at the Comedie Italienne, UA069.005.DO.00007.00009
      People; Theater; Opera houses
    - J.-B. Greuze, study for A Marriage Contract (ca. 1761), UA069.005.DO.00007.00010
    - Charles Colle, La Partie de chasse de Henri IV, UA069.005.DO.00007.00011
    - P.-A. Monsigny portrait by Thévenin, UA069.005.DO.00007.00012
    - P.-A. Monsigny portrait by Thévenin in detail, UA069.005.DO.00007.00013
    - Grétry - portrait by élisabeth Vigée-Lebrun, UA069.005.DO.00007.00014; Vigee-Leburn, Elisabeth
    - Portrait of Gluck by Duplessis/Miger, UA069.005.DO.00007.00015
    - Opéra Comique (Salle Favart), ca. 1801, UA069.005.DO.00007.00016
      Building sites
    - Théâtre de la rue Feydeau, UA069.005.DO.00007.00017
    - Etienne-Nicolas Méhul - portrait by Ducreux, UA069.005.DO.00007.00018; Ducreux
    - Jacques-Louis David - "Antiochus et Stratonice", 1774; UA069.005.DO.00007.00019
    - Stratonice air - text & translation, 1774; UA069.005.DO.00007.00020
  - Music theory in practice in theory, UA069.005.DO.00008; Christensen, Thomas
    Delivered as part of the Ritter Colloquium Series sponsored by the Department of Music at Tufts University, September 17, 2003
    - Frederic Louis Ritter, UA069.005.DO.00008.00001; Unknown
      Illustration for Thomas Christensen's paper "Music Theory in Practice in Theory"
      Ritter, Frederick Louis
  - The music lover in seventeenth and eighteenth century England, 2003; UA069.005.DO.00009; Harris, Elllen T.
    Delivered as part of the Ritter Colloquium Series sponsored by the Department of Music at Tufts University, October 1, 2003.
  - Translating a Winter's Journey: Crossing cultural boundaries, 1839 -- 1849; UA069.005.DO.00010; Youens, Susan
    Delivered as part of the Ritter Colloquium Series sponsored by the Department of Music at Tufts University, November 19, 2003.
    Winterreise; Schubert, Franz
    - Silhouette of Nourrit, ca. 1839, UA069.005.DO.00010.00001; Unknown
      Illustration for Susan Youens' paper, Translating a Winter's Journey
      Nourrit, Adolphe
    - Title page and frontispiece from "40 melodies choises par F. Schubert", 1849, UA069.005.DO.00010.00002; Unknown
      Illustration from Susan Youens' paper Translating a Winter's Journey.
  - Atlas of the City of Boston. from actual surveys and official plans. Boston proper and Back Bay, 1898; UA069.005.DO.00011; G. W. Bromley & Co.
  - The Boston directory containing the city record, a directory of the citizens, and business directory: for the year commencing July 1, 1885., UA069.005.DO.00012; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
  - Collected Poems of John Holmes, 2002; UA069.005.DO.00013; Holmes, John
    This text is a compilation of several poems by John Holmes.
    Poems; Holmes, John
  - High on the Hill, 1979; UA069.005.DO.00014; Dixon, Linda J.
    This pamphlet-style publication was created to inform incoming students of the history and traditions of Tufts University in the form of a self-guided tour of the Medford campus.
  - The Boston directory containing the city record, directory of the citizens, business directory, and street directory with maps for the year commencing July 1, 1905., UA069.005.DO.00015; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    This is an electronic edition of Sampson & Murdock Co.'s Boston city directory for 1905. It includes the A-Z personal directory section, along with page images of advertisements and other sections.
  - The Centennial History of Tufts College, 1952, UA069.005.DO.00016; Jumbo Book
    The Centennial History of Tufts College was initially published as a supplement to the Jumbo Book of 1952.
  - Stimpson's Boston Directory; containing the names of the inhabitants, their occupations, places of business, and dwelling houses, and the city register, with lists of the streets, lanes and wharves, the city officers, public offices and banks, and other useful information., 1845; UA069.005.DO.00017; Stimpson, Charles
    This is an electronic edition of Charles Stimpson's Boston city directory for 1845. It includes the A-Z personal directory section, along with page images of advertisements and additional sections.
  - The Boston directory, embracing the city record, a general directory of the citizens, and a business directory for the year commencing July 1, 1870., UA069.005.DO.00018; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    This is an electronic edition of Sampson, Davenport, & Co.'s Boston city directory for 1870. It includes the A-Z personal directory section, along with page images of advertisements and additional sections.
  - The Boston directory, embracing the city record, a general directory of the citizens, and a business directory for the year commencing July 1, 1872., UA069.005.DO.00019; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    This is an electronic edition of Sampson, Davenport, & Co.'s Boston city directory for 1872. It includes the A-Z personal directory section, along with page images of advertisements and additional sections.
  - The Boston directory, embracing the city record, a general directory of the citizens, and a business directory for the year commencing July 1, 1875., UA069.005.DO.00020; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
  - The Boston directory, embracing the city record, a general directory of the citizens, and a business directory for the year commencing July 1, 1865., UA069.005.DO.00021; Adams, Sampson & Co.
    This is an electronic edition of Sampson, Davenport, & Co.'s Boston city directory for 1865. It includes the A-Z personal directory section, along with page images of advertisements and additional sections.
  - Atlas of the city of Boston. Boston Proper and Back Bay from actual surveys and official plans., 1928; UA069.005.DO.00025; G. W. Bromley & Co.
    This is an electronic version of G. W. Bromley & Co.'s 1928 Atlas of the city of Boston, which includes page images of 36 plates, along with map and street indices.
    Boston (Mass.) - Maps.
  - Stories of the Streets of London, 1899; UA069.005.DO.00026; Baker, H. Barton
    London (England)--Description and Travel
  - Living Picture of London, for 1828 and Stranger's Guide Through the Streets of the Metropolis, UA069.005.DO.00027; Bee, Jon
  - The million-peopled city, 1853; UA069.005.DO.00028; Garwood, John
  - Society in London, by a Foreign Resident, 1885; UA069.005.DO.00029; Smalley, George W.
  - Social Life in the Reign of Queen Anne, taken from original sources, Volume II, 1882; UA069.005.DO.00030; Ashton, John
  - Farringdon Without History of the Most Interesting Places, Leading Events; and Some Account of the Eminent Men connected therewith, since the year 1600, 1870; UA069.005.DO.00031; Francis, Adolphus Decimus
  - The Joyous Neighbourhood of Covent Garden A Literary Souvenir of the Tavistock Hotel, Done in Celebration of its Hundredth Anniversary, 1887; UA069.005.DO.00032; Pascoe, Charles Eyre
  - Temple Bar: The City Golgatha A narrative of the historical occurances of a criminal character associated with the present bar, 1853; UA069.005.DO.00033; Wilson, James Holbert
  - Problems of a Great City, 1887; UA069.005.DO.00034; White, Arnold
  - College Acquires the English Collection of Late Professor Edwin C. Bolles, 1921; UA069.005.DO.00035; Boston Evening Transcript
    Books
  - History of England, Part I For the use of Middle Forms of Schools, 1898; UA069.005.DO.00036; Tout, T. F.; Powell, F. York
    In-text illustrations for this text are cataloged in MS004/002.001#DO01.
  - History of England, Part II From the Accession of Henry VIII to \tthe Revolution of 1689, 1898; UA069.005.DO.00037; Tout, T. F.; Powell, F. York
  - History of England, Part III, William and Mary to 1887, 1898; UA069.005.DO.00038; Tout, T. F.; Powell, F. York
  - Dictionary of National Biography, Index and Epitome, 1903; UA069.005.DO.00039; Lee, Sidney
  - Collectors and Collecting, 1898; UA069.005.DO.00040; Bolles, Edwin C.
    Collections
  - Old London Street Cries and the Cries of Today, 1885; UA069.005.DO.00041; Tuer, Andrew W.
  - Tom Brown's School Days, 1869; UA069.005.DO.00042; Hughes, Thomas
    Schools
  - London at the End of the Century:A Book of Gossip, 1900; UA069.005.DO.00043; a Beckett, Arthur William
  - England under Charles II. from the Restoration to the Treaty of Nimeguen, 1660-1678: English History from Contemporary Writers, 1889; UA069.005.DO.00044; Taylor, W. F.
  - Social Life in Queen Anne's Reign, Volume I., 1882; UA069.005.DO.00045; Ashton, John
  - A History of London, Vol. I, 1883; UA069.005.DO.00046; Loftie, W. J.
  - A History of London, Vol. II, 1883; UA069.005.DO.00047; Loftie, W. J.
  - In and Out of London Or, the Half-holidays of a Town Clerk, 1880; UA069.005.DO.00048; Loftie, W. J.
  - Kenna's Kingdom: a Ramble Though Kingly Kensington, 1881; UA069.005.DO.00049; Brown, R. Weir
  - Memorials of the Tower of London, 1866; UA069.005.DO.00050; De Ros, William Lennox
  - The Old Court Suburb, or Memorials of Kensington, Regal, Critical, and Anecdotical Volume I, 1855; UA069.005.DO.00051; Hunt, Leigh